Contact

anumulamurali@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/muralidharanumula (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Data Analysis Machine Learning Python

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Hindi (Limited Working)
Telugu (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Tensorflow: Getting Started
Digital Image Processing with
OpenCV in Python

Sentiment Analysis with Recurrent Neural Networks with Tensorflow

Online Workshop on 'The Apparel Recommendation Engine'

Muralidhar Anumula

Data Scientist at Muse Wearables

Bengaluru

Summary

Experienced Machine Learning Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the Information Technology and Product Development industry. Skilled in Python, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, Statistical Data Analysis and Algorithms. Strong Engineering Professional with a Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.) focused in Computer Science and Engineering from Santhiram Engineering College.

Experience

MuseWearables

1 year

Data Scientist

December 2019 - Present (9 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Data Science Intern

September 2019 - December 2019 (4 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Building Social Media Influencer marketing Tool which will analyse an Influencer Social Media profiles and generates an report with various metrics using Statistics, Machine Learning and Deep Learning Models.

CONZUMEX INDUSTRIES PRIVATE LIMITED

1 year

Data Scientist

December 2019 - Present (9 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Data Science Intern

September 2019 - December 2019 (4 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Building Social Media Influencer marketing Tool which will analyse an Influencer Social Media profiles and generates an report with various metrics using Statistics, Machine Learning and Deep Learning Models.

Freelance, self-employed
Freelance Machine Learning Engineer
January 2019 - September 2019 (9 months)

Hyderabad Area, India

Worked on Building Sentiment Analysis models on Hotel Reviews data provided by client.

Trained couple of students on Machine Learning and Deep Learning.

AgNext Technologies

Jr Machine Learning Engineer

October 2018 - December 2018 (3 months)

IIT Kharagpur

Worked on Building Pest classification Models for various crops and Quality Analysis Models for various Commodities. Lead Interns team. Delegated tasks, generated and shared comprehensive and detailed reports about team performance, mission-related objectives and deadlines.

KrishiHub Machine Learning Intern February 2018 - April 2018 (3 months) Bengaluru Area, India

Worked on Creating Demand Forecasting Model(from Scratch) and also Improved the performance of the existing Price Forecasting Models.

Education

Applied Al Course
Machine Learning · (2017)

Santhiram Engineering College
Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Computer Science and
Engineering · (2013 - 2017)